<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tic-tac-toe on Savakar Rohan&#39;s site</title>
    <link>https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/tags/tic-tac-toe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tic-tac-toe on Savakar Rohan&#39;s site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 17:42:09 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/tags/tic-tac-toe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MENACE #02</title>
      <link>https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/mathematics/menace02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 17:42:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/mathematics/menace02/</guid>
      <description>Lets take a moment to revise everything so far;
 We learnt that we tend to reward good behaviour while reprimanding unfavourable ones. We learnt that states represent the factors which influence a person&amp;rsquo;s decision. We learnt that the most recent state effects the players future decisions more than previous states  The actual computer Now to the dirty business, how shall we make this computer? We saw that the states are independent of each other and primarily a decision is based purely out of the most recent state, so it makes sense to have containers of all the possible states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MENACE #01</title>
      <link>https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/mathematics/menace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 17:42:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://savakarrohan.github.io/website/mathematics/menace/</guid>
      <description>The Matchbox Educable Noughts and Crosses Engine (MENACE)is a mechanical computer made from 304 matchboxes designed and built by Donald Mitchie in 1961.
What? During world war II when computers were essentially mechanical devices and women crunching numbers, there was an interest to make a computer to learn by itself. Eager to demonstrate artificial intelligence through &amp;ldquo;trial and error learning&amp;rdquo; in simple mental games he constructed a device out of matchboxes to test out his algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
